https://www.diabeticcandy.com/security-privacy.html

Security & Privacy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which DiabeticCandy.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of this website (each, a "User").
Privacy:
Users’ privacy is very important to DiabeticCandy.com.
DiabeticCandy.com is committed to safeguarding the information Users entrust to DiabeticCandy.com.
Returns:
We do not accept returns.
If something breaks during transit, we will deal with it on an individual basis.
The information DiabeticCandy.com collects:
DiabeticCandy.com may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where Users are invited to volunteer such information. DiabeticCandy.com may also collect information about how Users use our website, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the website or the domains from which Users originate. We may use "cookies" to track how Users use our website. A cookie is a piece of software that a webserver can store on the Users’ PC and use to identify the User should they visit the website again. While not all of the information that we collect from Users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that Users provide us through our website.
How DiabeticCandy.com uses information:
DiabeticCandy.com may use personally identifiable information collected through our website to contact Users regarding products and services offered by DiabeticCandy.com and its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners, and otherwise to enhance Users’ experience with DiabeticCandy.com and such affiliates, independent contractors and business partners.
Disclosure of information:
DiabeticCandy.com does not disclose personally identifiable information collected from Users to any outside organizations without the prior consent of the User. If you have any questions about this policy, or feel it is not being enforced properly, please contact Diabetic Candy.com at arlene@DiabeticCandy.com
Anti-Spam Policy
DiabeticCandy.com has a zero tolerance policy with regards to spam. Spam is defined as mass unsolicited email to people who have not opted-in to receive your email or email to people with whom you do not have a prior relationship established.
For ISPs and Internet Blacklist Maintainers:
DiabeticCandy.com does not allow the sending of spam. Violators of this policy will be blacklisted. Contact us at arlene@DiabeticCandy.com with any questions or complaints.
For Email Recipients:
If you feel that you have received unsolicited email from DiabeticCandy.com on the DiabeticCandy.com web site, please report this to abuse arlene@DiabeticCandy.com. You may also call us at 973-446-5684. DiabeticCandy.com has a zero tolerance policy with regards to spam.
General Legal Matters:
DiabeticCandy.com's Privacy Policy governs DiabeticCandy.com's collection, storage, and use of information gathered through this website. DiabeticCandy.com customers are subject to DiabeticCandy.com's Acceptable Use Policy.
Designation of Agent for Notification of Claims of Infringement
Copyright Notice:
All contents of this website are copyright © 2010, DiabeticCandy.com All rights reserved.
Trademark Notices:
DiabeticCandy.com, the DiabeticCandy.com logo, and certain other marks in this website are the trademarks, trade names, and service marks of DiabeticCandy.com. Any use of such marks without the prior written consent of DiabeticCandy.com is prohibited.
Contact Us
Diabetic Candy.com, LLC
P.O. Box 138Hibernia, NJ 07842
arlene@diabeticcandy.com
973-446-5684
diabeticcandy.com
Links
Chocolates
Security & Privacy
All of our products are sugar freeMost of our delicious treats are sweetened naturally with Maltitol or Hydrogenated Starch Hydrolysate, but none of our sweets have refined sugar.Links to other Diabetic Sites
Copyright ©  diabeticcandy.com, Diabetic Candy.com, LLC. All rights reserved.
